[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Almaty, or Alma-Ata as formerly known, is the largest city and capital of which country?", "correct_answer": "Kazakhstan", "incorrect_answers": ["Krgyzstan", "Tajikistan", "Kyrgyzstan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the diet of Green iguanas?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Young iguanas are known to eat the feces of mature iguanas.", "Wild iguanas sometimes eat bird eggs.", "They are primarily herbivorous."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thieves, rapists, gang members and psychopaths lie in wait under their victims cars and slash their victims Achilles tendon so they cant escape. When did this urban legend begin circulating?", "correct_answer": "The 1950s", "incorrect_answers": ["The 1970s", "The 1920s", "The 1990s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Because of his notable achievements as a poet, writer, and independence movement leader, Jose Marti is considered the greatest hero of which country?", "correct_answer": "Cuba", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Mexico", "Argentina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Les Barker, Richard Digance and Bill Oddie are famous for being what?", "correct_answer": "Musical comedians", "incorrect_answers": ["Radio comedians", "Impersonators", "Satirists"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many species of penguins live in warm or even tropical environments?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["0", "3", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Mercurys spin-orbit resonance?", "correct_answer": "3:2", "incorrect_answers": ["1:1", "8:5", "3:4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A very complicated Honda Accord commercial required 606 takes and was done without the use of any computer-generated images.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The following group of words (as a whole) makes up a palindrome:\nA man.  A plan.  A canal.  Panama.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At wedding ceremonies in China, both the bride and the groom are dressed in this color.", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue", "Silver", "Yellow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "WETYIAFHKLXVNM\nQRUOPSDGJCB\nIn which of these rows would the letter Z  go?", "correct_answer": "top", "incorrect_answers": ["none", "neither", "bottom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The organ of Corti, named after Alfonso Corti, is located in this body part of mammals.", "correct_answer": "Inner ear", "incorrect_answers": ["Forebrain", "Mammary gland", "Eye"]}]